Contact

<u>cuong.trieu2207@gmail.com</u>

Phone: 093 526 4625

www.linkedin.com/in/viet-cuong-a92705182 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills C# .NET VB.NET ORACLE MS.SQL



Trieu Viet Cuong

Dot Net Software Engineer

Vietnam

Date of birth: 22/07/1995

Summary

About me $= \{$

isCSharpDeveloper: true,

loveToWorkWith: ['HTML', 'JS', 'CSS', 'C#.NET', 'MS.SQL',

'Node', 'PHP', 'MySql'],

hasJoined: ['FPT Software', 'Robert Bosch Engineering', 'CMC-

Global'],

hobbies: ['Sport', 'Music', 'Photography', 'Technologies']

};

Strong experience in developing with 4 years working in the IT field

Strong knowledge of .NET architecture

Knowledge of Scrum process, team working, review code

Ability to think and Research to resolve the problem

Possess a Can-Do attitude, excellent communication, and problemsolving skills

Experience

CMC-Global

(12/2020 - curent)

Intage AI – Development team

	Ţ
Customer	Japan
Description	Manage cutting industrial tools, manage and binding
	the coordinate defects
Team size	6
Position	Team leader
Main responsibilities	Implement back-end function
	Support technical to teammate
	Work closely with the project manager to provide
	the solution
Technical	.NET 5, Azure: SQL, Block storage, App service,
	Service bus

Contact

cuong.trieu2207(a)gmail.com

Phone: 093 526 4625

www.linkedin.com/in/viet-cuong-a92705182 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills C# .NET VB.NET ORACLE MS.SQL SMG – Development team

(03/2021-curent)

Customer	America
Description	The system that manages the customer feedback,
	generates the modernized report base on customer
	feedback
Team size	6
Position	Senior engineer
Main responsibilities	Implement new features to the existing system
	Fix bug production
	Upgrade angular JS to typescript
Technical	Angular JS, Angular typescript, .NET Framework,
	MongoDB, Google analytics (Angulatics)

Bosch Engineering and Business Solutions Software Engineer

CI-CAT – Development team

03/2019 – 12/2020 (1 year 9 months)

Customer	Germany
Description	ERP product manage user, role, asset, charging
Team size	6
Position	Developer
Main responsibilities	Implementation
	Support technical and mentor a new member
	Work closely with the Operations team for
	production issues
	Work closely with the Client for change request
Technical	.NET Framework, Oracle, VB.NET, Window Form,
	WCF service

Flexible Seat Booking project – Development team 12/2019 – 02/2020 (3 months)

Customer	Viet Nam
Description	Internal tool management and booking seats for
	employee
Team size	6
Position	Developer
Main responsibilities	Implementation new feature of flexible seat
Technical	.Net Core, Asp .Net MVC, MS.SQL, JavaScript,
	Ajax, jQuery, Web API

Contact

cuong.trieu2207@gmail.com

Phone: 093 526 4625

www.linkedin.com/in/viet-cuong-a92705182 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills C# .NET VB.NET ORACLE MS.SQL

FPT Software

P3.M35 – Function Development team

11/2017 – 03/2019 (1 year 5 months)

Customer	Japan
Description	ERP systems related to the asset, finance, and user with
	a large amount of traffic
Team size	200
Position	Developer
Main responsibilities	Create a design document based on the function
	specs
	Coding, Unit Test, Deploy
Technical	.NET Entity Framework, Angular 4, MS.SQL,
	Web API, Active report

Technical Skill

- HTML, CSS, JS, Ajax, jQuery, Angular JS, TypeScript
- C# .NET, Web API, JSON, LINQ
- Unit testing: N Unit, Jasmine
- Design: Coding solid, Design Patterns, OOP
- Database: MS.SQL, ORACLE
- Cloud: Azure
- Source control: Git, SVN, TFS
- Tracking project: JIRA, CONFLUENCE
- OS: Linux(Fedora), Windows

Education

Hong Bang University International HIU

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology (2013 - 2017)

University of Science Ho Chi Minh City

Complete the PHP programmer training program (05/2016 - 10/2016)